<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Luiz Macedo</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/</link><description>Recent content on Luiz Macedo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020 LUIZ MACEDO'S BLOG is licensed under CC BY 4.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 04:45:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luizmacedo.dev/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure DevOps Agent Latest Version</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/azure-devops-agent-latest-version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 04:45:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/azure-devops-agent-latest-version/</guid><description>The best way to handle this at the moment is to get the latest release from the GitHub API and then use the version tag from that to create the download URL for the specific platform you want.
The release object has an assets.json file associated with it with the download links for each package if you want to avoid hard-coding the URL scheme.
Here is a PowerShell example that could be easily adapted to any language:</description></item><item><title>Azure Devops Service Tag NSG Rule</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/azure-devops-service-tag-nsg-rule/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 11:00:17 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/azure-devops-service-tag-nsg-rule/</guid><description>If you need to enable the Service Tags for your NSG or Firewall pointing to the Azure DevOps Service tag, run:
az network nsg rule create -g MYRESOURCEGROUP &amp;ndash;nsg-name MYNSG -n AzureDevOps &amp;ndash;priority 400 &amp;ndash;source-address-prefixes VirtualNetwork &amp;ndash;destination-address-prefixes Storage &amp;ndash;destination-port-ranges &amp;lsquo;*&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash;direction Inbound &amp;ndash;access Allow &amp;ndash;protocol Tcp &amp;ndash;description &amp;ldquo;Allow Azure DevOps Services.&amp;quot; The Service Tag does not apply to Microsoft Hosted Agents. Customers are still required to allow the entire geography for the Microsoft Hosted Agents.</description></item><item><title>Surface Laptop 3 UEFI Boot</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/surface-laptop-3-uefi-boot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 11:53:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/surface-laptop-3-uefi-boot/</guid><description>Quick tip for the Surface Laptop 3 owners.
During this week, after a Windows update, I had a problem with my Surface Laptop 3. It was unable to start Windows at all. I tried several times to enter the setup following the recommendations, but without success.
I needed to change the boot to start the flash drive to recover the operating system, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t. After a lot of work to find the information and wasted time, I found out how to boot the Surface UEFI.</description></item><item><title>5 years at Microsoft, my lucky story!</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/five-years-at-microsoft-my-luck-history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 10:00:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/posts/five-years-at-microsoft-my-luck-history/</guid><description>This week on Sep 1, 2019, it&amp;rsquo;s been 5 years that I am lucky to work in the biggest IT company in the world. The dream company which I finally joined at 25 years old.
Luck doesn&amp;rsquo;t come from 5 years back. That luck started in 2004 &amp;ndash; 15 years ago when I was 15 years old. I started to go to Technical High School. This luck led me to receive an offer to start my first internship for 2 or 3 months at the Data Processing Laboratory of Colégio Bagozzi, right after starting my technical course.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luizmacedo.dev/en/pages/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a DevOps Support Escalation Engineer at Microsoft.
I code, write, speak, empower, promote, learn and listen.
Opinions are my own.</description></item></channel></rss>